Patience Oladayo Oladele

Customer Success Manager Saas

Pontoise (95) 95300 patoladele@gmail.com +33 (0) 7 58 39 00 23

A bilingual professional with a zest for learning and self-development. I possess a blend of business and technical skills to contribute to the growth of organizations. 3+ years' experience in business development, sales and customer facing roles. Above all I am passionate about software development and new technologies.

Expérience

Product Developer

Cryptoplayground - Remote janvier 2021 - décembre 2021

Empathy planning, User personas, UX design, Front-End development, usability testing, wireframing, prototyping of mobile and web interface

Customer Success Manager---->Country manager France

Radiant Melanin London - London août 2019 - novembre 2020

Tracked customer satisfaction, Educated customers on products, develop strategies for client retention, organized sales events, demand planning and logistics monitoring London-France, Budgeting, Business localization and translation services, identified opportunities for new product propositions, client data analysis, B2B and B2C sales, UX design, social media and communication, customer service, Monthly reporting, partnership and collaboration management

International Damage Recovery Consultant

Enterprise Holdings - Paris (75) juillet 2017 - février 2019

Summary:Customer advisory and training, client portfolio/account management, client and team member onboarding, sales and customer service

Drove consumer sales and provided customer service for one of America's car rental company at the Paris head office analysing, accelerating, advising and giving recommendations on over 100 portfolios weekly.

Liaising with other business stakeholders to be able to establish the right damage recovery approach for each customer.

Establishing and maintaining relationships with internal and external insurance brokers, clients and partners

Spearheading team stat report preparation to top management for sales and KPI tracking. Responsible for handling insurance claims, damage recovery files, customer contracts, repair invoices/accounts.

Coaching, supervising and preparation of training materials for new recruit.

Coordinated and planned new software improvements. Analyses of departmental work processes an clearly communication and collaborating with the IT team needs and specifications.

Restructuring of team processes to meet the new objectives and goals of the business.

Business Developer

Augmented Intelligence Institute IVS - Copenhagen, DK juillet 2016 - octobre 2016

Summary:Created innovative pricing strategies and CRM that helped satisfy present clients and keep track of potential customers

Collaboratively worked with the Senior management team to maximize opportunities and generate sales activity with clients and partners.

Researched on emerging markets and technology trends

Established relevant client profile and use case scenarios via analysis of current and potential clients

Generated systematic approaches to reach new clients in a chosen market.

Data extraction using Google analytics and social media platforms

Lead service pricing activity through analysis of competitors and established pricing range based on industry standards.

Key achievement: Creation of innovative pricing strategies and CRM that helped satisfy present and keep track of potential customers

IT Application Analyst

Port Harcourt Refining Company NIGERIA octobre 2014 - janvier 2015

Change management of risks associated with 4 main application servers

- # Analysis of staff IT skill set to aid custom made training materials
- # Analysis of departmental workflow to aid design of new automated systems.
- # Increased awareness of innovative ideas to top management.
- # Designed and developed a company-accessible prototype platform for task assigning and KPI Key achievement: Overall, stock taking was made effective and downtimes reduced. There was an increase in productivity of software interfacing by 45% and increase in transparency and IT department's KPIs by 40%.

Formation

Bachelors - Computer Engineering en Computer Science

Covenant University - Ota juillet 2013 - septembre 2018

Masters International Business en Business international

Grenoble Ecole De Management - Grenoble (38)

janvier 2015 - septembre 2017

Compétences

Microsoft Suite (10 ans minimum)

- SQL (1 an)
- Project Management (2 ans)
- Analytic problem solving (3 ans)
- Business process development (2 ans)
- Leadership and team management (3 ans)
- Good communication skills
- stratégie commerciale (Moins d'un an)
- User Experience (UX)
- User Interface (UI)
- JavaScript
- HTML5
- Agile
- SaaS
- Java
- React (1 an)
- Linux (3 ans)
- Figma (2 ans)
- Cloud computing (1 an)
- UNIX (1 an)
- Bootstrap (2 ans)
- Product development (2 ans)
- Leadership
- Gestion de point de vente
- Supervision
- Sens de l'organisation

Languages

- French Fluent
- English Expert

Liens

http://linkedin.com/in/oladeleoladayo

https://github.com/DidiVerte

Groupes

Carregeo Environnement

août 2021 - aujourd'hui

Group advocationg for environment change.

I give my time to the cause by helping with website widgets and content localization

Informations complémentaires

EXTRA PROFESSIONAL ACTIVITIES

- Analysis of market trends and product innovation at ARIESPAK
- Fundraising, outsourcing of services and communication audits with partners/sponsors for Go-Karting company, SPEEDWAY KARTS
- Project management and outsourcing of branding services for metallurgy company, BLUEFINITY
- Served under the NATIONAL YOUTH SERVICE CORPS programme as a computer studies teacher in addition to working on community development projects and fund generation.